Despite having devoured the five continents
五つの陸を食らい尽くし
and slurping the three oceans dry,
三つの海を飲み干しても
the sky alone remains out of reach...
空だけはどうすることもできない
...for this body of mine that
lacks wings, hands, and feet.
翼も手も足もないこの身では
〔発射〕
我は世界蛇
I am the World Serpent.
My name is...
我が名はヨルムンガンド
...Jormungand.
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
一，二，三，四...
much the same
其实都一样
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
日听   yaya
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
日听      奶昔
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない でも傷つけたくもない
矛 or 盾? 不想认输 可是又不愿受伤害
I don't want to lose,
but I don't want to hurt anyone either
时轴      两仪
I took it so I could confirm
手に取って 確かめてた
先挑一样在手中仔细掂量
That there's definitely no going back
きっと戻れないんだって
可是发现再要反悔为时已晚
Whose side are you on?
你选的是哪边?
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Memories are shackles
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
Don't want to know!  思念是枷锁
注释   TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) A postscript love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
Don't want to know!  追悔莫及的爱
后期  aoi
(Don't want to know!) Your kindness is a disservice
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
Don't want to know!  温柔是弱点
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
压制   娜夏
With your arms out wide, keep balanced
広げる両手 keep balance
张开双臂保持平衡
Go the direction that lets you fly higher
より高く飛べる方へ
向着更高的天空振臂而飞
I want to protect
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
唯独想保护的是.. 背负于我们那折翼的背膀之上的
What our wingless backs here bore:
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
两仪
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
F-22战斗机：F-22战斗机（猛禽）是由美国洛克希德·马丁、波音和通用动力公司联合设计的新一代
重型隐形战斗机。也是专家们所指的"第四代战斗机"。它将成为21世纪的主战机种。
主要任务为取得和保持战区制空权，将是F-15的后继型号。
父さんと母さんを殺したのは
Mother and Father were killed by
a cutting-edge fighter jet like that one.
ああいう最新鋭の戦闘機 新型の爆弾
It used a new type of bomb...
Those who invent weapons, those who make them,
武器を考える奴
USSR AKM：全长876mm 重量3.40kg 口径7.62mm*39 装弹数5/20/30/40/75/180+1
连射速度600发/分 发射形式S/F 制造国：苏联
造る奴
those who sell them, and those who use them--
売りさばく奴
使う奴
I will hate them forever.
僕は
永遠に憎む
I'm not sure if God knows how I feel or not, but...
そんな気持ち 神は知ってか知らずか
Walk briskly, Officer Jonah!
きりきり歩けー ヨナ隊員
C'mon! One, two! One, two!
ほら イッチニ イッチニ イッチニ イッチニ
One, two! One, two!
This is the young weapons dealer
who goes by Koko Hekmatyar.
ココ·ヘクマティアルと名乗った若いウェポン·ディーラー
I traveled with a weapons dealer.
僕は
武器商人と旅をした
"Gunmetal Calico Road"
I traveled with a weapons dealer.
What was once my crew of eight subordinates
今までの8人の私の部下がちょうどここで集まってる
just so happens to be here.
Now that we've got you, it's up to nine.
君が入ると9人だ
They're all weirdos,
but there's no need to be afraid.
変な人ばっかだけど ビビることないよ
I know this is your first time meeting them,
初の顔合わせなのに
残念だがゆっくりはしてられない
but unfortunately we can't take it easy.
See, we've got a problem.
問題が起きてね
It's why we're stuck out in
the boonies in Eastern Europe.
東欧の片田舎で足止め食ってる理由なんだけどね
You're going to help resolve the problem.
問題の解決を手伝ってもらう
FN Hi-Power MK3：全长200mm 重量986g 口径9mm*19 装弹数13/20 制造国：比利时
It's an enlistment ceremony for joining my unit
私の部隊への入隊儀式の一つ
そして君の性能のテストでもある
as well as a means to test your performance.
Mao, Wilee!
マオ ウェリ
Koko, who's the kid?
ココさん その子はいったい
Him?
この子
Guys, attention!
皆 注目
This is Jonah.
彼がヨナだよ
新人って少年兵だったのかよ
The new recruit was a boy soldier?
He's strappin' a heater. Scary!
チャカ持ってる
コェエ
Now, now! Don't freak out.
はいはい ビビるな
トージョ
Tojo, explain our current predicament
so he knows what's going on.
彼にも分かるよう現状の説明
It hasn't changed.
変わらんね
"Our" container is being held up at the port.
我らのコンテナは港で足止め食らったまんま
The Ministry of Home Affairs
Central Customs Security Force
そいつを指示した内務省中央税関保安隊にはココさんからお電話願います
which issued those orders,
wants you to call them, Koko.
They never planned on letting it slip through.
連中最初から通す気ないよ
というわけで 私たちの持ち物を取り返さなければならない
So we've gotta get our goods back. Okay?
オーケー
I don't care about that.
そんなことはどうでもいい
All I need to know is who
and where to shoot. That's all.
必要なのは「どこで誰を撃つか」 それだけ
レーム
Lehm! Valmet!
バルメ
Prepare to set out! Hop to it!
出動準備 準備
Miss Hekmatyar, are you
saying this with the full knowledge
ミスヘクマティアル
貴女は「あのコンテナ」が
我が国に及ぼす影響を知った上で言っているのかね
of how that "container" would affect our country?
We cannot let it fall into
the hands of our government.
我々はあれを軍に引き渡すわけにはいかん
If you insist upon forcing your way through,
それでも強行するというのなら
we will take appropriate measures to stop you!
それ相応の手段を取るぞ
Don't do anything you'll regret, bitch!
後悔するなよ 小娘
Right back at you.
そりゃこっちの台詞だ
ヨナ どう 新しい仲間は
Jonah, what do you think of your new comrades?
Nothing much...
別に
You're such a poop!
スレたやっちゃのお
I thoroughly researched you when I hired you.
君を雇うにあたって 君をとことん調べた
どこで生きて どこで戦ったか
Where did you live and where did you fight?
What do you like and dislike?
何が好きで 何が嫌いか
Why did you get booted from your old group?
何をやって古巣を追い出された
You hate weapons, don't you, Jonah?
武器が嫌いなんだね ヨナ
Is answering me too much of a pain?
返事をするのも嫌なのか
I hate talking.
喋るのが嫌いなんだ
I hear you. But that won't cut it from today on.
分かるよ でも今日からはそれじゃ通らん
で どうよ バルメ
So, whadda ya think, Valmet?
Oh, are you referring to Jonah?
あ ヨナ君のことですか
He hasn't said a word yet,
so I can't answer that question.
まだ一言も喋ってないのに どうよ言われても困ります
でもまあ 気配の鋭さは尋常じゃないですね
But his heightened senses aren't normal.
Koko's in danger!
ココが危険です
She's alone in a car with that boy soldier!
あんなヤバ気な少年兵と二人きりで車に乗って
She's always like this when we get a new recruit.
新入りが来るといっつもこうです
She gets overly excited!
張り切りすぎて ここに何かあったら
If anything happens to her,
I'll do him in before killing myself.
彼をバラして 私も死にます
Hey, Lehm! Don't smoke
just because we're alone!
ちょっと レーム
二人しかいないからって煙草止めて下さい
Not in this tight space!
こんな密閉空間で
Yeah, yeah.
はいはい
何時の間に火つけたんですか
When did you light that?
It's going to make my hair stink!
髪に匂いが付きます
Hey...
ねえ
Yes? Yes? Ask anything!
何 何 何でも聞いて
How does this unit handle people trailing us?
この部隊での尾行者の扱い
The first to strike wins!
そりゃもう
先手必勝 一撃必殺
Kill 'em in one blow!
FN FNC：全长1000m 重量4.445kg 口径5.56*45 装弹数20/30 发射形式S/F/3 制造国：比利时
He's flickin' them off!
弾きやがった
Jonah!
ヨナ
Jonah! Jonah!
ヨナ ヨナ
撃つ前くらい何か言ってくれないかな
Could you warn me before you fire?!
You made me jump outta my skin!
びっくりするから
Don't be ridiculous.
そんな無茶な
Those were scouts.
The real battle's coming up.
今のは拙攻だ
次からのが本番
Weapons dealer Koko Hekmatyar's
container is stuck at my port.
武器商人ココ·ヘクマティアルのコンテナを俺の港で止めた
The air force must never get
their hands on those monstrosities.
空軍の手に渡ってはいけない代物だからだ
Curious what's inside?
中身が知りたいか
米格－29战斗机，是苏联70年代开始研制的超音速、高性能、有单双座型双发战斗机。它由前苏联
米高扬飞机设计局研制，高尔基等多家飞机制造厂生产，1983年开始装备部队。
北约组织给予的绰号是"支点"(Fulcrum)
A kit that would update three squadrons
worth of our primary fighter jets.
我が国の主力戦闘機三個飛行隊分の近代化改修キット
It would put our aerial forces on par
with that of our neighboring countries.
我が国と周辺諸国との空軍力を均衡をさせるほどの代物だ
If our military authorities got this,
これが軍部に届き戦闘機に実装されたその時から我が国は
the moment it's implemented our country will...
At any rate, don't let the police step in.
とにかく 警察は介入するな
There's a gunfight?
銃撃戦が始まってる
Pretty much. I sent my men in,
so don't worry about it.
まあな 俺が部隊を投入したんだ 心配するな
If they make it to the port, I've lost.
奴らが港に着いちまったら俺の負けだ
I'm hanging up.
切るぞ
M249Para：全长914（766）mm 重量7.1kg 口径5.56mm*45/7.62mm*51
装弹数30/弹链 连射速度750~1000发/分 发射形式F 制造国：美国
That van is really tough.
すっごく硬いんですけど
And it'd stink if it counterattacked.
あのバン
反撃ウザイですし
It's totally blockin' the road.
キッチリ塞いでやがるなあ
If we don't hurry,
私達が急がないと前方にいるココが挟み撃ちになってしまいます
Koko's going to get hit from both
sides since she's ahead of us.
そのつもりだろうよ
That's probably what they're goin' for.
Lehm, could you get right up to that van?
レーム バンにぴったりくっつけてもらえます
You serious?
マジかよ
Koko, the left lane!
ココ 左車線
Reinforcements?
新手
Missy, let's go on a drive to the port!
お嬢ちゃん 港までドライブしようぜ
BOCXOR6
Voskhod 6?! Damn that old fart!
ボスホート６
あのオッサンめ
H&K Mark 23 (US Mk.23 Mod.0)：全长245mm 重量1210
口径.45ACP 装弹数10/12+1 制造国：德国
H&K MP5 (HK54)：全长680mm 重量2.54kg 口径9mm*19 装弹数15/30/40
连射速度800rpm 发射形式S/F 制造国：德国
Roar!
It looks like the two in the back
dealt with those trackers.
後ろの二人は追っ手を片付けたみたいだよ
No one has fired at us
since we left the freeway.
こっちといえば 高速を降りたとたん撃ってこなくなった
ヨナ さっきさ ココって呼んでくれたでしょ
Jonah, didn't you just call me Koko?
That didn't slip past me.
聞き逃さないんだから
--I like that! It made me happy! I hope you--
--Koko! Koko!
あれいいなあ 嬉しいよ これからずっと
ココ ココ
It's time to say, "Goodbye."
お別れの時間だってさ
Later, Miss Weapons Dealer!
じゃあな 武器商人ちゃん
伏せて
Get down!
Fly to the moon!
月まで吹っ飛ぶよ
It's an anti-tank missile.
対戦車ミサイルだ
A Javelin ATGM?!
ジャベリンATGM
Lockheed Martin "Javelin"：全长1200mm 重量22.3kg
弹头：纵列式成型装药弹头 装弹数1 制造国：美国
笑った 次弾装填まで20秒
He laughed?
Twenty seconds until he reloads!
It's okay. I won't let him fire it again.
大丈夫 次は撃たせない
All trackers and security from the
Hewlett Bonded Area Port: Pull back.
尾行及びヒュレト港保税区画保安要員撤退
Voskhod 6 officers, pull back.
ボスホート６ 総員撤退せよ
I repeat: Voskhod 6, pull back.
繰り返す ボスホート６ 総員撤退せよ
Now our country will plummet into war.
これで我が国は戦争へところに落ちていく
I'd bet on it.
賭けてもいい
It's out of my hands now.
俺にはもう止められん
例えば
Let's assume you killed me, a weapons dealer,
今ここで私という武器商人を殺し
and marked one person off your vengeance list.
君の復讐を一つ達成したとしよう
Then you'd force your way through
my surrounding subordinates and flee.
君は取り囲んだ私の部下を蹴散らして逃亡する
Despite their appearances,
they're actually quite formidable.
あんな様子だが 彼ら 結構手強いぞ
So what would you need to achieve your goal?
そのために使わざるを得ない物は
Right, a gun.
そう 銃だ
Can you toss aside your guns?
君は銃を捨てられるか
Nope. You'll never put your weapons down.
無理だね
君は一生武器を捨てられない
You hate them more than anyone,
そいつに対する憎しみは誰よりも強いが
but you also know better than
anyone just how handy they can be.
そいつを持つことの頼もしさを誰よりも知っているから
Follow me, Jonah. I am a weapons dealer.
私に付き従え ヨナ
私は武器商人 君とそいつの付き合い方教えてやる
And I will teach you how to hang out with them.
Why do you sell weapons, Koko?
ココはなぜ武器を売る
For world peace.
世界平和のために
起きろ ヨナ坊
Wake up, Little Jonah.
It's time for your rounds.
巡回の時間だよ 交代してくれ
Swap out with me.
Go team up with that old fart, Lehm.
レームのおっさんと組め
Were you actually asleep?
お前 ちゃんと寝てる
It's cold, so be sure to get dressed.
寒いからちゃんと着ろな
I'm dead tired!
超ねみ
Good morning.
おはよう
Morning.
...はよ
Oh!
It's unusual for you to ask a question!
珍しいね 君から質問だ
So you're basically sayin' this, right?
要するにこうだろ 俺のような凄腕 百戦練磨 超絶傭兵が
It's weird for an amazing, awesome
mercenary who's seen a hundred battles
to work for some young weapons dealer chick.
ココっていう小娘 武器商人に従ってるのが不思議
I don't recall praising you.
あんたを褒めた覚えはないよ
It's probably hard to tell since
you've only been here for a few days.
まだ行動を共にして数日のヨナには難しいだろうがな
俺の答えは
My answer'd be...
...because it's fun.
「おもしろいから」
--Koko, that hurt!
ココ 痛いです 寝ぼけてますね
--I imagine everyone has their own reasons.
--Koko, that hurt!
他の連中だってそれぞれ理由があるんじゃねの
--I imagine everyone has their own reasons.
--You're still half asleep!
--Valmet, I'm sorry.
--You'll develop a reason of
your own and start to understand
--Valmet, I'm sorry.
君にだって 理解ができてくるし 分かってくる
what it means to be part of the unit
and how Koko is an excellent...
部隊に自分がいる意味
ココってのがどれだけ優秀な
An excellent... what?
優秀な なんだっけ
The bathroom's inside, Koko.
トイレは中だぜ ココ
There's an emergency!
緊急事態だ
三時間前 北の国境から入国した輸送団
Three hours ago, a transport team
came in through the northern border.
If the information and count is correct,
情報とカウントが正しければ
they're carrying the Mi-24D attack
helicopters, AKA the Hind D.
こいつの中には戦闘ヘリコプター Mi-24D
Mi-24D Hind D：米-24"雌鹿"武装直升机D型，Mi-24D与其他构型相比是更偏向纯炮艇设计，
1973年投产，Mi-24D前机身大幅修改设计，两个驾驶舱是隔绝分开的，一是专职驾驶一是专职炮手，
一门12.7mm四管机枪于机鼻下，还可装四具57mm火箭莱舱，四具9M17 Phalanga反战车导弹
（比Mi-24A的MCLOS系统有大幅跃进），也可安装传统炸弹。
すなわち 「ハイドD」
これの十五機分が分解され
Fifteen of them have been dismantled and
stuffed together with a kit containing spare parts.
予備部品一式と共に詰まっている
Someone heard about our recent success
これはこの間の私たちの成功を聞いた誰かが
and wants to try a hand at it...
「俺にも一枚かませろ」と参入したものにほかならない
...going by this timing.
タイミング的に
But this happens a lot.
でもこんなことはよくあること
The problem is that...
問題は この情報が「本部」から送られてきたこと
...this info came from HQ.
If we botch this up, they'll dock our pay.
へますると給料減らされる
This is bad!
やばいよ
あの転がりっぶりは相当やばいって意味だぜ
The way she's rolling around means this is really bad.
状況を開始する
We'll crack down on the situation.
Intercept the enemy's delivery!
敵商品の納入阻止
There is a strong chance that hard negotiations
邪魔者の排除を含む ハードネゴシエーションになる確率が高い
will include eliminating obstacles.
Keep focused!
気を引き締めろ
ウエー
'Kay...
Nah, I'll let everyone focus in their own way...
いや やっぱ 引き締め方は各人に任せる
Valmet, you and Tojo handle negotiations
with the national defense's headquarters.
バルメ トージョと共に 国防軍司令部でネゴ
レーム ウゴ ルツ マオは武装 私の直援に回れ
Lehm, Ugo, Lutz, Mao, gear up!
You'll be my backup.
Wilee, R, stay here and
consolidate mine and HQ's info.
ウイリ アール ここにいて私と上との情報整理
Jonah, come with me.
ヨナ 私とこい
Let's go!
行くぞ
ココ·ヘクマティアルだ
Koko Hekmatyar here. Code: Orange.
コンデイ オレンジ 繰り返す コンデイ オレンジ
I repeat, Code: Orange!
Uh-huh. Did you tell
the movers it's off as of today?
引越し業者に今日中止って伝えてくれた
Sure did, Mr. Kloshkin.
はい クロシキンさん
Hm, then you can go home now.
じゃあ 君も帰っていいよ お疲れさま
You've done well!
C·K·クロシキン
C. K. Kloshkin?
Right. He's a freelance weapons dealer.
そう フリーランスの武器商だ ヨーロッパで活動
He works in Europe.
Rumor has it he's a has-been secret agent.
噂じゃ 諜報員くずれやれなんやら ソイツだと思うよ
I think he's our man.
それをちゃんと伝えたんですか
Were you sure to tell her that?!
What'll we do if he's dangerous?
危ない奴だったらどうしましよう ココが心配です
I'm worried about Koko!
She already knows without me having to tell her.
俺がら言わなくても分かってるって
Besides, Ms. Koko has five guys with her.
それにココさんには五人も付いてってんだぜ
姉御は俺の身を案じるべきだよね 実際
Chief, you should be worried about me, really.
No. Tojo, you're fully capable of fighting.
いやです
トージョは自分で戦えるじゃないですか
I'll only risk my life for Koko.
私が命かけるのはココだけです
Seriously?
マジで
What if we're negotiating with
someone like an agent from The Matrix?
交渉相手が「メイトリックス大佐」みたいのだったら どうすんだよ
约翰·梅屈克上校：电影《魔鬼司令》中的一个角色，阿诺饰演。
I'd abandon you and run for it.
トージョ置いて逃げます
Take this with you, Jonah.
これをもっておくんだ ヨナ
Colt Government (US M1911) ：全长216mm 重量1077g
口径.45ACP/.38Super 装弹数7+1/9+1 制造国：美国
--I have my own.
--Yeah, it's a spare.
自分も持ってる
うん 予備
I've heard some rumors and more
detailed info has been coming in.
噂は聞いてたし
さっきか詳細も届くんだけど
He's a real jerk...
ちょっと嫌な相手だなあ
Of course, everyone in
this line of work's unpleasant.
この業界嫌な奴ばかりだけど
Wow, awesome!
おお スッゲェ
What is?
なに
She said to "hunt."
「狩れ」だってさ
久々の狩じゃ
We haven't hunted in ages.
It's huntin' time!
狩じゃ
Sometimes our boss can be extreme!
俺らのボスは時々過激だぜ
Jonah, you aren't a soldier this time.
ヨナ 君は今回兵士でばなく そうだなあ
Let's see...
I want you to pretend you're my brother.
「弟」を演じてほしい
No matter what happens to me,
keep the farce up until I give the signal.
私が合図するまで 私に何があっても
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kloshkin.
始めまして ミスタークロシキン
I am Koko Hekmatyar.
ココ·ヘクマティアルと申します
うん ＨＣＬＩミスヘクマティアル 知ってるよ
Yeah, Miss Hekmatyar of HCLI. I've heard of you.
HCLI：军火集团Hecmatial的简称，之前蔻蔻口中的本部就是指军火集团本部
Sorry, I just moved in.
ごめんね 越したばかりでさ
It's such a mess, I can't find my card.
ごちゃってて こっちの名刺埋もれてる
Well, take a seat. I can get you some coffee.
掛けてくださいよ コーヒーなら出せる
Would the boy like some cola?
僕はコーラがいいかな
Actually, who is this kid?
て言うか この坊っちゃんはなに
Hmm, your brother?
弟さん
Well, I think I know why you're here.
何しに来たかは分かってるつもりだよ よろしく
Let's get to work.
You want me to cancel the Hind D's delivery, eh?
ハインドDの納入中止と言われましてもね
I think that would be hard,
although I won't say it's impossible.
難しいと思いますよ
できないとは言わないが
Even amongst our air force's leaders,
I lean on the side of the dove.
私も空軍首脳の中ではハト派寄りだ
But see, that recent deal with your boss
でもね この間のあなたのボスの件ね
has made us put some thought
into updating our Fulcrums.
ファルクラムの近代化改修にはいろいろ考えさせられた
支点：苏联制米格29
Please let me speak with Hekmatyar.
ヘクマティアルに連絡させれください
Good, he's taking the bite.
いいぞ それは食いついているんだ
Use the anti-aircraft missiles card.
空対空ミサイルのカードを切れ
Sorry about that.
失礼
What was with that?
That was a random spurt of coolness.
何それ いきなりかっこいいね
So we're getting into a bidding war?
安売り合戦始ちゃうんだ
You're all set to fight.
もはや喧嘩腰じゃん
No sense of comradeship as fellow dealers in arms?
兵器を扱う者同士って考え方はなしかい
Nope. I don't see things that sweetly.
ないね
そんな優しい思考は持ち合わせがない
This is basically what you've done:
あんたがやったのはつまりはこうだ
You tried to slip a cow into my lush pasture
私が育てた牛の豊かな牧場に
and raise it there amongst my herd.
こっそりと羊を放って育てようとして
俺だ
It's me.
I don't know who put you up to it,
誰のそそのかされたか 知らんが
but don't blame me if you get shot by a cowboy.
カウボーイに撃たれても仕方ないな
ふざけんじゃねえぞ
Screw you!
撃つな
Don't fire!
That's right. Nothing good
would come from shooting me.
そうだ 撃ってもロクなことないからな
情報の通りかよ
So my info was right.
少年兵なんぞ連れやがって
You're totting around a boy soldier.
あんた俺以上のクソかもな
You might be an even bigger piece of shit than me.
男前になったじゃん
You look masculine now!
Missy, I hear you've got a bunch of personal guards,
お嬢ちゃん あんた結構な数の私兵を持ってるらしいが
but don't pull any stunts.
妙な真似すんなよ
スナイパーだ 頭消し飛ぶぜ
I've got snipers! They'll blast your head off!
帰りたくなりました 帰っていいですよ
Want to go home? You're welcome to leave.
The Hind's delivery is right on track.
ハインドも順調に移動してます
But from now on we're
going to work as business part--
ただ 今後もビジネスパートナーとしての口約束くらい
You're a simple-minded man, Kloshkin.
おめでたい男 クロシキン
Huh?
うん
Hint: My eyes.
ヒント 私の目
Take a good look at my eyes.
私の目をよく見ることだ
You're reflected off of my eyes,
but I'm afraid I don't see you.
この目にはお前が反射しているが
悪いが私はお前など見ていない
We deal with steel killing machines called "weapons,"
武器という鋼鉄の殺人機械を扱う我々だが
その取引は人と人との駆け引きなのだ
but each transaction is a battle of wits
played by the people involved.
テメェ 何だそりゃ
You bitch! What are you going on about?!
I'm glad cells are waterproof these days.
最近の携帯は防水で良かった
I warned you! Do anything weird--
言ったぜ 妙な真似すな
スナイパーか
Your snipers? Why don't you give them a call?
掛けてみたら
Hey, Lehm! Should I shoot? Should I?
おい レーム
撃っちまう 撃っちまうか
I wouldn't.
やめとけ
Hey.
Huh? Who're you?
あれ お前 誰
Oh, hey. It looks like we got them all.
どうもこれで全部みたいです
よくやった 早急に撤退しろ
Well done. Pull back immediately.
Here's the last one.
ラスト
Right now, your life is worth a single sheet of paper.
今 お前の価値は紙きれ一枚
そうです 二重線で消して
That's right.
Cross it out with two lines and
then sign next to it to prove it was you.
それをまたご自分のサインで証明してください
Miss Koko, we've suppressed the Hinds.
ココさん ハインド押さえまして
The contract with Kloshkin...
クロシキンの契約書ですが
...has just left the Colonel's hands.
たった今 大佐の手を離れました
Bang!
Koko!
ココ
It's superficial. Head wounds just bleed a lot.
浅い
頭の血は派手に見える 運がいいね
You're lucky.
All done! All done!
終わった 終わった
Let's go home.
帰ろ 帰ろ
So this is what guys who sell weapons are like.
武器を売る奴は こんな奴だったのだ
Although they may not be the norm...
異端なのかもしれないけど
...I think I'm going to stick with them.
付いて行ってみようと思う
僕は武器商人と旅をした
I traveled with a weapons dealer.
We'll meet up with Valmet
and Tojo in the next town over.
バルメとトージョは次の町で合流
We leave at 9:00.
出発は九時だ
What did you think of working with the boss?
どうだったよ ボスの仕事は
I let her get hurt.
怪我させた
Wasn't it part of the plan?
作戦の内だろ
Don't sweat it, kiddo.
がきがあんなこと 気にしてんなっての
Think good and hard as to why she
keeps having you cook egg-based dishes.
どうして卵料理ばかり作らされてるのか よく考えるこったな
Hungry belly! Hungry belly!
腹減り 腹減り
This is the welcoming ceremony to my unit.
これが私の隊の入隊儀式だ
As of today, you are an egg in a new army,
national organization, and family.
君は今日 軍 国家 組織 家族を一新した タマゴ君だ
Welcome to having reliable comrades, Jonah.
頼もしい仲間を歓迎するよ ヨナ
N-Nasty... This is nasty...
不味い
これ 不味い
The ocean god reclines against the light,
光横たえる海神
光怪陆离的海底龙神
His mistake wavering along the scar
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累创痕之间摇曳着缕缕罪孽
He rises to the surface and takes a breath
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐浊
For he has obtained a love
and hate that only dissolve and blend
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
爱与恨 如漆似胶 如影随形
His dream leans toward
矛盾孕む
矛盾诞世
The sound of the scheme
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的梦中 世界渐渐倾浸于欺言诡语之中
That shall encompass this
world fraught with contradictions
He no longer has legs
脚は もう無い
足膝 已没入虚无
His heartbeat pierces through the watery wall
水壁を貫く鼓動
透过水壁 传来阵阵鼓动..
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
翻译 TL旧民        日听 yaya
注释 TL旧民        日听 奶昔
后期 aoi           压制 娜夏
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
时轴 两仪
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"